http://www.ohiochristian.edu/about/privacy-policy

Employment
We know that you care how your information is used, and we appreciate your trust that we will use it carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By submitting information through our website(s), you are accepting the privacy policy described below.  (Last revised 12/31/18)
Information You Provide:
Ohio Christian University collects data from you in several ways including non-personal information. Non-personal information may include, but is not limited to, the OCU portals you click and the type(s) of devices you use.
Cookies: OCU reserves the right to use “cookies.” Cookies are small programs that transfer to a visitor’s device enabling us to recognize you and provide you with a more customized browsing experience. Using cookies enhances your browsing experience and is optional.
Protecting Your Personal Information: We receive and store the personally identifiable information you enter such as name, address, phone number, and other information submitted via the website. We use the information you provide in order to respond to your requests and to improve our website. The information collected is never sold, rented, or leased outside of University partners and initiatives.
Third Party Websites: Although you may see an Ohio Christian University ad on a different website, it does not mean that OCU has any control over what that website contains nor does the university endorse its content or messaging. When using a third-party website, you are subject to their privacy policy.
Changes to this privacy statement: Ohio Christian University reserves the right to make any change to this privacy policy at any time. When an update occurs, the revised edition and the new publication date will be published on the OCU website. You are encouraged to read through this frequently to ensure you have seen the most recent version.
Accepting these terms and conditions: By using any OCU website you are agreeing to the terms and conditions within this policy. It is your responsibility to have read through the privacy policy and that by doing so and continuing to operate within the websites, you agree with its content. If you do not agree with the content, please refrain from using OCU websites
A-Z
Admissions and Aid
Athletics
All Degrees and Programs
MyOCU
Login
Alumni
Contact
Privacy Policy    Student Consumer Information    Title IX - Report an Incident    © Ohio Christian University
Chat with us, powered by LiveChat
